Guide to the Robert R. Nathan papers, 1943-1975
Nathan, Robert R. papers, 1943-1975
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert R. Nathan Papers, 1944-1973
4410
Robert R. Nathan, 1908-
1.7 cubic ft.
Typescript travel diaries.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Typescript travel diaries describing Nathan's consulting work in countries including Afghanistan, Burma, Colombia, Costa Rica, El Salvador, Israel, Korea, Malaysia, Nigeria, and Vietnam.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Robert Nathan heads the firm of Robert R. Nathan Associates, consultants for economic devleopment.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Typescript travel diaries describing Nathan's consulting work in countries including Afghanistan, Burma, Colombia, Costa Rica, El Salvador, Israel, Korea, Malaysia, Nigeria, and Vietnam.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Nathan, Robert R., 1908-
Subjects:
Consultants.; Economic development.
Places:
Afghanistan--Description and travel.; Burma--Description and travel.; Colombia--Description and travel.; Costa Rica--Description and travel.; El Salvador--Description and travel.; Israel--Description and travel.; Korea--Description and travel.; Malaysia--Description and travel.; Nigeria--Description and travel.; Vietnam--Description and travel.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Palestine, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Paris, Aug., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sweden-Poland, May, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Israel, Sept. 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Far East, June 1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Burma-Israel, Aug., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Round-the-World; Burma, Feb. 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Korea-Burma, Oct. 1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Burma-Israel, Feb. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Burma, July, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Burma-Israel, Feb. 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Burma, Aug., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Burma, July, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Burma, Feb. 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Round-the-World; Burma, Feb. 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Columbia, Feb. 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Burma, Jan. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Burma, Feb. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Iran, Nov. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Afghanistan, May 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Afghanistan, Oct. 1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Afghanistan, May, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Korea, Dec. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- El Salvador, Feb. 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Afghanistan, Apr., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- El Salvador, Aug., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Nigeria, Feb. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Afghanistan, Mar., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- El Salvador, Apr., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Korea, Part I, Aug. 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Korea, Part II, Aug., 1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Costa Rica, Jan. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- El Salvador, Feb. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Afghanistan, India, Israel, Mar., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Saipan and Korea, Apr., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Saipan and Korea, Part II, Apr., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- El Salvador, Oct. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Afghanistan, Nov. 1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Vietnam conference in Hawaii, Feb. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Afghanistan, Apr., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Costa Rica, May, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Korea, June, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Afghanistan, Nov. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Afghanistan, Mar., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Israel, Mar., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Israel, Aug., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Israel, Jan. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Israel, Mar., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Malaysia, Apr., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Afghanistan, Jan. 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Switzerland, etc., Apr., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Afghanistan-Nepal, Dec., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Afghanistan, Tehran-Israel, Aug., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Afghanistan, May, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Afghanistan, Nov. 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Far East, Korea, July, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Files on Burma, 1943-1962 (Box 3)